recruitadvantage.com 2013-12-08

# Privacy - RecruitAdvantage

This document provides information on how we handle your personal information and the content in this site.

## Type of Personal Information Held

Personal information that we collect and hold usually falls into the following categories:

  Information gathered for subscription purposes for the company newsletter or news feeds;

  Candidate Information submitted and obtained from the Candidate and other sources in connection with applications for work;

  Work performance information;

  Staff information;

  Information submitted and obtained in relation to absences from work due to leave, illness or other causes;

  Information obtained to assist in managing client and business relationships;

## What your 'personal information' is

Personal information is any information or an opinion (whether true or not) about you. It may range from the very sensitive (e.g. medical history or condition) to the everyday (e.g. address and phone number). It would include the opinions of others about your work performance (whether true or not), your work experience and qualifications, aptitude test results and other information obtained by us in connection with your possible work placements. Personal information includes 'sensitive information'.

## What 'sensitive information' is

Sensitive information is a special category of personal information. It is information or opinion about your: racial or ethnic origin; political opinion; membership of a political association or religious beliefs, affiliations or philosophical beliefs; membership of a professional or trade association or membership of a trade union; sexual preferences or practices; criminal record; health or disability (at any time); expressed wishes about the future provision of health services. It includes personal information collected to provide a health service.

## Purposes for which we hold Personal Information

We primarily hold personal information for the following :

  Recruitment & Placement operations

  Training

  Marketing

  Staff management

  Client and business relationship management

## Who will be collecting your personal information?

Your personal information will be collected by RECRUITadvantage for its own use and on behalf of other associated parties to RECRUITadvantage who might require access to your personal information in connection to the purposes for which we hold Personal Information.

## How your information will be collected

Personal information will be collected from you directly when you subscribe to our feeds/newsletters and/or submit a resume and/or provide any other information in connection with your application to us.  
Personal information will also be collected when:

  we receive any reference about you

  you provide us with any additional information about you.

## Accuracy of Information

This Site has been prepared from information believed to be accurate and reliable at the time it was sourced. Information is updated on a regular basis.

No company within the RECRUITadvantage Group, nor any director, employee or agent of RECRUITadvantage, gives any guarantee, representation or warranty as to the reliability, accuracy or completeness of the information on the Site, nor accepts any responsibility or liability arising in any way (including by reason of negligence) for errors in, or omissions from, the information on the Site. This does not limit any rights a person may have under the Trade Practices Act. Subject to the law, RECRUITadvantage does not accept any responsibility, or owe any duty of care, to any person acting, or refraining from acting, as a result of information on the Site.

## Disclosures

RECRUITadvantage has privacy guidelines in place to ensure the confidentiality of any personal details you choose to provide through this Site. We will not provide information that would personally identify you to third parties unless we have first sought your permission, except that we may disclose your personal information where we are under a legal duty to do so, including circumstances where we are under a lawful duty of care to disclose information.

## Terms and Conditions of the Site

Every time you access or browse this Site you are deemed to accept the Terms and Conditions of the Site.

You may reproduce any part of the content of the Site, however if you do so, you must acknowledge RECRUITadvantage's copyright in that content, and retain all markings that indicate the origin of the content. You must not otherwise reproduce that content.

Notwithstanding anything else in these Terms and Conditions, you must not reproduce any content from the Site for a commercial purpose or for a profit making purpose.

Use of the Site is at your risk. To the extent permissible by law, RECRUITadvantage disclaims all liability arising out of or consequent on any:

**a)  **access by you to the information available from the Site;  **  
b)  **infection by any computer virus which occurs as a result of accessing the Site or any of the content contained on the Site; or  **  
c)  **use of any information or content available from the Site.

By sending any information to RECRUITadvantage you agree to indemnify RECRUITadvantage and all of its employees, officers and agents from any loss suffered by them as a result of any use of, or reliance on that information.

## Links to other sites

RECRUITadvantage has not reviewed any URL linked to or from any part of the Site and is not responsible for any content found at these URL's.

Once you leave RECRUITadvantage 's site we can not control the information you access. The presence of a hyper-link from this site does not imply any kind of endorsement by RECRUITadvantage of the content of the linked site. Each individual site has its own set of policies about what information is appropriate for public access.
